A Guide to the Correspondence and subject files of the Virginia Secretary of Administration and Finance, 1976-1985.
Library of Virginia
- Correspondence and subject files, 1974-1985 (Accession 37778)., Extent: x cubic feet (x boxes)
  - Budget 1978-1980 Biennium (Dept. of Planning and Budget) - Six Year Expenditure Plan, 1977. (Box 25)
  - Budget 1978-1980 Biennium (Dept. of Planning and Budget) - Identification / Analysis, 1977. (Box 25)
  - Budget 1978-1980 Biennium (Dept. of Planning and Budget) - 27T Forms, 1975-1976. (Box 25)
  - Budget 1978-1980 Biennium (Dept. of Planning and Budget) - Capital Outlay, 1977. (Box 25)
  - Budget, Division of, 1977. (Box 25)
  - Central Accounting, 1977. (Box 25)
  - Central Garage, 1977. (Box 25)
  - Compensation Board, 1977. (Box 25)
  - Comptroller, 1977. (Box 25)
  - Conservation and Economic Development, Dept. of, 1977. (Box 26)
  - Consolidated Laboratories, Div. of, 1977. (Box 26)
  - Consultant firms, 1977. (Box 26)
  - Corrections, Dept. of, 1977. (Box 26)
  - Council of State Governments, 1977. (Box 26)
  - Crime Commission, Virginia, 1977. (Box 26)
  - Delinquent accounts, 1977. (Box 26)
  - Elections, State Board of, 1977. (Box 26)
  - Emergency Services, Office of, 1977. (Box 26)
  - Employment Commission, Virginia, 1977. (Box 26)
  - Energy, State Office of, 1977. (Box 26)
  - Engineering and Buildings, Div. of, 1977. (Box 26)
  - Equal Employment Opportunity, 1977. (Box 26)
  - Fire Commission, 1977. (Box 27)
  - Freedom of Information, 1977. (Box 27)
  - Governmental Management, Commission on, 1977. (Box 27)
  - Governor's Office, 1977. (Box 27)
  - Governor's Advisory Board on Revenue Statements, 1977. (Box 27)
  - Governor's Budget Advisory Committee, 1977. (Box 27)
  - Governor's Committee on Employing the Handicapped, 1977. (Box 27)
  - Governor's Employee Advisory Committee, 1977. (Box 27)
  - Governor's Mansion, 1977. (Box 27)
  - Governor's News Statements, 1977. (Box 27)
  - Governor's Year End Statement, 1977. (Box 27)
  - Health, Education and Welfare, U.S. Dept. of, 1977. (Box 27)
  - Health, Virginia Dept. of, 1977. (Box 27)
  - Higher Education, Council of, 1977. (Box 27)
  - Historic Landmarks Commission, 1977. (Box 27)
  - Housing Development Authority, Virginia, 1977. (Box 27)
  - Housing and Urban Development, U.S. Dept. of, 1977. (Box 27)
  - Housing, Office of, 1977. (Box 27)
  - Intergovernment Affairs, Dept. of (#1), 1977. (Box 28)
  - Intergovernmental Affairs, Dept. of (#2), 1977. (Box 28)
  - Intergovernmental Affairs, Dept. of - Planning Districts, 1977. (Box 28)
  - Interstate Cooperation Commission, 1977. (Box 28)
  - Joint Legislative Audit and Review Commission, 1977. (Box 28)
  - Labor, U.S. Dept. of, 1977. (Box 28)
  - Labor and Industry, Dept. of, 1977. (Box 28)
  - Land use, 1977. (Box 28)
  - Legislation, 1977. (Box 28)
  - Legislation - Testimony of MBR on S 1437, 1977. (Box 28)
  - Legislative Liaison Person, 1977. (Box 28)
  - Library, Virginia State, 1977. (Box 28)
  - Legislative tracking system, 1977. (Box 28)
  - Legislators - Federal, 1977. (Box 28)
  - Legislators - State, 1977. (Box 28)
  - Local Government, Advisory Council on, 1977. (Box 28)
  - Management Analysis and Systems Development, Dept. of, 1977. (Box 29)
  - Management Analysis and Systems Development, Dept. of - Management Analysis Reports, 1977. (Box 29)
  - Management and Budget, U.S. Office of, 1977. (Box 29)
  - Methods Studies of Administration and Finance, 1977. (Box 29)
  - Mental Health and Mental Retardation, Dept. of, 1977. (Box 29)
  - Miller, Ronald (MIS Director), 1977. (Box 29)
  - National Governors Association, 1977. (Box 29)
  - Personnel and Training, Dept. of, 1977. (Box 29)
  - Personnel and Training, Dept. of - Memoranda, 1977. (Box 29)
  - Personnel and Training, Dept. of - Memoranda to agencies, 1977. (Box 29)
  - Personnel and Training, Dept. of - Personnel Study (HJR 64), 1977. (Box 29)
  - Personnel and Training, Dept. of - Positions, 1977. (Box 30)
  - Personnel and Training, Dept. of - Positions vacant, 1977. (Box 30)
  - Program Budgeting - Administration and Finance, 1977. (Box 30)
  - Property of the Commonwealth, 1977. (Box 30)
  - Purchase and Supply, Dept. of, 1977. (Box 30)
  - Register Committee, 1977. (Box 30)
  - Schools, Fran, 1977. (Box 30)
  - Science and Technology, 1977. (Box 30)
  - Science Museum of Virginia, 1977. (Box 30)
  - Secretary of the Commonwealth, 1977. (Box 30)
  - Secretary of the Commonwealth - Appointments, 1977. (Box 30)
  - Southern Celebration, 1977. (Box 30)
  - Southern Governor's Conference, 1977. (Box 30)
  - Sum Sufficient Appropriation - Quarterly reports, 1977. (Box 30)
  - Supplemental Retirement System, Virginia, 1977. (Box 30)
  - Secretary of Commerce and Resources, 1977. (Box 31)
  - Secretary of Education, 1977. (Box 31)
  - Secretary of Human Resources, 1977. (Box 31)
  - Secretary of Public Safety, 1977. (Box 31)
  - Secretary of Transportation, 1977. (Box 31)
  - Assistant Secretary of Financial Policy, 1977. (Box 31)
  - Spurlock, James B., 1977. (Box 31)
  - Taxation, Dept. of, 1977. (Box 31)
  - Telecommunications Council, 1977. (Box 31)
  - Human Resources, Office of - Public Relations and Public Resources, 1975. (Box 31)
  - Human Resources, Office of - Regionalization, 1974-1975. (Box 31)
  - Simms, Janice, 1979. (Box 31)
  - Appointment calendars (Finney), 1975-1977. (Box 31)
  - Accounts, Dept. of - CARS system, 1978. (Box 32)
  - Administration and Finance, Office of, 1978. (Box 32)
  - Appropriations Committee, 1978. (Box 32)
  - Appropriations Committee - Contacts, 1978. (Box 32)
  - Art Commission, State, 1978. (Box 32)
  - Auditor of Public Accounts, 1978. (Box 32)
  - Audit reports, 1978. (Box 32)
  - Budget (Dept. of Planning and Budget), 1978. (Box 32)
  - Budget (Dept. of Planning and Budget) - Administration and Finance, 1977. (Box 32)
  - Budget (Dept. of Planning and Budget) - Commerce and Resources, 1978. (Box 32)
  - Budget (Dept. of Planning and Budget) - Education, 1977. (Box 32)
  - Budget (Dept. of Planning and Budget) - Higher Education, 1978. (Box 32)
  - Budget (Dept. of Planning and Budget) - Overview, 1978. (Box 32)
  - Budget (Dept. of Planning and Budget) - Public Safety, 1977. (Box 32)
  - Budget (Dept. of Planning and Budget) - Transportation, 1977-1978. (Box 32)
  - Cabinet car mileage, 1978. (Box 32)
  - Cabinet meeting minutes, 1978. (Box 32)
  - Cabinet Secretaries, Memoranda to, 1978. (Box 32)
  - Central Accounting, 1978. (Box 32)
  - Chamber of Commerce, Virginia State, 1978. (Box 32)
  - Compensation Board, 1978. (Box 32)
  - Comptroller, 1978. (Box 32)
  - Comptroller - Accounting system, 1978. (Box 32)
  - Comptroller - Revenues, 1978. (Box 32)
  - Coal - Issues, 1978. (Box 33)
  - Collections agencies, 1978. (Box 33)
  - Commerce, Dept. of, 1978. (Box 33)
  - Commission on the Status of Women, 1978. (Box 33)
  - Community Colleges, Dept. of, 1978. (Box 33)
  - Community Services Adiministration, 1978. (Box 33)
  - Computer Services, Dept. of, 1978. (Box 33)
  - Conferences and workshops, 1978. (Box 33)
  - Confidential reports, 1978. (Box 33)
  - Consolidated Laboratories, Div. of, 1978. (Box 33)
  - Consolidated Laboratories, Div. of - Forensic science, 1978. (Box 33)
  - Corrections, Dept. of, 1978. (Box 33)
  - Council of State Governments, 1978. (Box 33)
  - Crime Commission, Virginia State, 1978. (Box 33)
  - Data Center, State, 1978. (Box 33)
  - Data Processing Procurement, 1978. (Box 33)
  - Data Transmission Network, 1978. (Box 33)
  - Direct Deposit System, 1978. (Box 33)
  - Directive System - Questions/Problems, 1978. (Box 33)
  - Directives - Dept. of Personnel and Training, 1978. (Box 33)
  - Eastern Virginia Medical Authority, 1978. (Box 33)
  - Education Assistance Authority, 1978. (Box 33)
  - Education Subcommittee - House (H 375), 1978. (Box 33)
  - Elections, State Board of, 1978. (Box 33)
  - Emergency and Energy Services, State Office of, 1978. (Box 33)
  - Emergency Proclamations, 1978. (Box 33)
  - Emergency Services, Dept. of, 1978. (Box 33)
  - Employee Assistance Program, 1978. (Box 33)
  - Employee Relations Counselors, Dept. of, 1978. (Box 33)
  - Employment Commission, Virginia, 1978. (Box 33)
  - Equal Employment Opportunity, 1978. (Box 33)
  - Equal Employmnet Opportunity - Colleges and Universities, 1978. (Box 33)
  - Executive orders, 1978. (Box 33)
  - Executives loaned, 1978. (Box 33)
  - Federal Funds Utilization, 1978. (Box 34)
  - Federal Regional Council meeting, 1978. (Box 34)
  - Fire Commission, 1978. (Box 34)
  - Football tickets, 1978. (Box 34)
  - Freedom of Information, 1978. (Box 34)
  - General Services, Dept. of, 1978. (Box 34)
  - General Services, Dept. of - Engineering and Buildings, Div. of, 1978. (Box 34)
  - General Services, Dept. of - Engineering and Buildings, Div. of - Surplus Property, 1978. (Box 34)
  - Government Advisory Council, Local, 1978. (Box 34)
  - Governmental Management, Commission on State, 1978. (Box 34)
  - Governor, 1978. (Box 34)
  - Governor Dalton, 1978. (Box 34)
  - Governor's Office - Jennifer Joy Mansen, 1978. (Box 34)
  - Governor's Office - Larry Murphy, 1978. (Box 34)
  - Governor's Office - Press releases, 1978. (Box 34)
  - Governor's Employee Advisory Committee, 1978. (Box 35)
  - Health, Virginia Dept. of, 1978. (Box 35)
  - Health, Education and Welfare, U.S. Dept. of, 1978. (Box 35)
  - Higher Education, Council of, 1978. (Box 35)
  - Hopkins Commission, 1978. (Box 35)
  - Housing and Community Development, Dept. of, 1978. (Box 35)
  - Housing Development Authority, 1978. (Box 35)
  - IBM, 1978. (Box 35)
  - Intergovernmental Affairs, Office of, 1978. (Box 35)
  - Intergovernmental Affairs, Office of - Interstate Cooperation Commission, 1978. (Box 35)
  - Intergovernmental Affairs, Office of - Planning districts, 1978. (Box 35)
  - Intergovernmental Affairs, Office of - Reorganization, 1978. (Box 35)
  - Justice and Crime Prevention, Div. of, 1978. (Box 35)
  - Juvenile Justice, 1978. (Box 35)
  - Kepone, 1978. (Box 35)
  - King and Associates, 1978. (Box 35)
  - Labor, U.S. Dept. of, 1978. (Box 35)
  - Land Management, 1978. (Box 35)
  - Legislation - Federal Status Reports, 1978. (Box 35)
  - Legislation - SJR 96, 1978. (Box 35)
  - Legislators - Federal, 1978. (Box 35)
  - Legislators - State, 1978. (Box 35)
  - Legislative Tracking, 1978. (Box 35)
  - Library, Virginia State, 1978. (Box 35)
  - Literary Fund, 1978. (Box 35)
  - Loans, 1978. (Box 35)
  - Local Debt, State Commission on, 1978. (Box 35)
  - Local Government Advisory Council, 1978. (Box 35)
  - Savings Bonds, U.S., 1978. (Box 36)
  - Schools, Fran, 1978. (Box 36)
  - Science, Virginia Academy of, 1978. (Box 36)
  - Secretary of the Commonwealth, 1978. (Box 36)
  - Smithsonian Folklife Festival, 1978. (Box 36)
  - Social Services Research Planning and Coordination Program, 1978. (Box 36)
  - Southern Center for International Studies, 1978. (Box 36)
  - Southern Governors Conference, 1978. (Box 36)
  - Southern Growth Policies Board, 1978. (Box 36)
  - State agency publications, 1978. (Box 36)
  - State Corporation Commission, 1978. (Box 36)
  - State employees and political activities, 1978. (Box 36)
  - State / Federal relations, 1978. (Box 36)
  - State mandate programs, 1978. (Box 36)
  - Study of the Feasibility of the State Insuring Its Own Vehicles, 1978. (Box 36)
  - Sunset Reports, 1978. (Box 36)
  - Supplementary Fiscal Assistance Act, President's, 1978. (Box 36)
  - Support Services, Dept. of, 1978. (Box 36)
  - Supreme Court, 1978. (Box 36)
  - Taxation, Dept. of, 1978. (Box 36)
  - Taxation, Dept. of - Replies to general inquiries, 1978. (Box 36)
  - Telecommunications Council, Virginia Public, 1978. (Box 36)
  - Travel requests, 1978. (Box 36)
  - Treasury, Dept. of the, 1978. (Box 36)
  - Treasury, Dept. of the - Unclaimed Property, 1978. (Box 36)
  - Treasury, Dept. of the / Treasury Board - Craigie proposal concerning Literary Fund monies, 1978. (Box 36)
  - Treasury, U.S. Office of the, 1978. (Box 36)
  - Unemployment Compensation Trust Fund, 1978. (Box 36)
  - United Givers Fund, 1976. (Box 36)
  - United Givers Fund, 1978. (Box 36)
  - United Way Campaign, 1978. (Box 37)
  - Urban Assistance Incentive Fund, 1978. (Box 37)
  - Urban Policy Status Report, President's, 1978. (Box 37)
  - USS Virginia, 1978. (Box 37)
  - VEPCO negotiations, 1978. (Box 37)
  - Virginia Community College System / Virginia Commonwealth University Consolidated Computer Facility, 1978. (Box 37)
  - Virginia Design Assembly - Proposed, 1978. (Box 37)
  - Virginia Institute of Marine Science, 1978. (Box 37)
  - Virginia Museum of Fine Arts Theater, 1978. (Box 37)
  - Virginia Polytechnic Institute and State University, 1978. (Box 37)
  - Vocational Rehabilitation, Dept. of, 1978. (Box 37)
  - Volunteerism, Office of, 1978. (Box 37)
  - Water Control Board, State, 1978. (Box 37)
  - Welfare, Dept. of, 1978. (Box 37)
  - William and Mary College of, 1978. (Box 37)
  - Word processing, 1978. (Box 37)
  - World Bank (Economic Development Institute), 1978. (Box 37)
  - Xerox, 1978. (Box 37)
  - Secretary of Commerce and Resources, 1978. (Box 37)
  - Secretary of Education, 1978. (Box 37)
  - Secretary of Human Resources, 1978. (Box 37)
  - Secretary of Public Safety, 1978. (Box 37)
  - Secretary of Transportation, 1978. (Box 37)
  - Assistant Secretary for Financial Policy, 1978. (Box 37)
  - Assistant Secretary for Financial Policy: Abandoned Vehicle Fund, 1978. (Box 38)
  - Assistant Secretary for Financial Policy: Accounting Project, State, 1978. (Box 38)
  - Assistant Secretary for Financial Policy: Administration and Finance, Secretary of (Charles B. Walker), 1978. (Box 38)
  - Assistant Secretary for Financial Policy: Administration and Finance, Secretary of - Agency meetings, 1978. (Box 38)
  - Assistant Secretary for Financial Policy, 1978. (Box 38)
  - Assistant Secretary for Financial Policy: American Society for Public Administration, 1978. (Box 38)
  - Assistant Secretary for Financial Policy: Accounts, Dept. of, 1978. (Box 38)
  - Assistant Secretary for Financial Policy: Alcoholic Beverage Control Board, 1978. (Box 38)
  - Assistant Secretary for Financial Policy: Auditor of Public Accounts, 1978. (Box 38)
  - Assistant Secretary for Financial Policy: Blue Cross / Blue Shield, 1978. (Box 38)
  - Assistant Secretary for Financial Policy: Bonds (General), 1978. (Box 38)
  - Assistant Secretary for Financial Policy: Budget Advisory Committee, Governor's, 1978. (Box 38)
  - Assistant Secretary for Financial Policy: Cabinet, 1978. (Box 38)
  - Assistant Secretary for Financial Policy: Capital Outlay Appropriations, 1978. (Box 38)
  - Assistant Secretary for Financial Policy: Clippings, 1978. (Box 38)
  - Assistant Secretary for Financial Policy: Commerce, Dept. of, 1978. (Box 38)
  - Assistant Secretary for Financial Policy: Commerce and Resources, Secretary of, 1978. (Box 38)
  - Assistant Secretary for Financial Policy: Commerce and Resources, Secretary of (HB 210 Study), 1978. (Box 38)
  - Assistant Secretary for Financial Policy: Commerce and Resources, Secretary of (HB 1206 Study), 1978. (Box 38)
  - Assistant Secretary for Financial Policy: Commerce and Resources, Secretary of (HB 1565), 1978. (Box 38)
  - Assistant Secretary for Financial Policy: Commissioners of Revenue, 1978. (Box 38)
  - Assistant Secretary for Financial Policy: Compensation Board, 1978. (Box 38)
  - Assistant Secretary for Financial Policy: Congressional members, 1978. (Box 38)
  - Assistant Secretary for Financial Policy: Connock, Stuart W., 1978. (Box 38)
  - Assistant Secretary for Financial Policy: Consolidated Laboratory Services, 1978. (Box 38)
  - Assistant Secretary for Financial Policy: Coopers and Lybrand, 1978. (Box 38)
  - Assistant Secretary for Financial Policy: Credit Union, State Employees, 1978. (Box 38)
  - Assistant Secretary for Financial Policy: Data Transmission Network Study, 1978. (Box 38)
  - Assistant Secretary for Financial Policy: D.C. Commuter tax, 1978. (Box 38)
  - Assistant Secretary for Financial Policy: Deferred compensation, 1978. (Box 38)
  - Assistant Secretary for Financial Policy: Deficit authorizations outstanding, 1978. (Box 38)
  - Assistant Secretary for Financial Policy: Digest of House Appropriations, 1978. (Box 38)
  - Assistant Secretary for Financial Policy: Education, Secretary of - Issue Analysis 70/30 Plan, 1978. (Box 38)
  - Assistant Secretary for Financial Policy: Education, Secretary of, 1978. (Box 39)
  - Assistant Secretary for Financial Policy: Elections, State Board of, 1978. (Box 39)
  - Assistant Secretary for Financial Policy: Emergency and Energy Services, Office of, 1978. (Box 39)
  - Assistant Secretary for Financial Policy: Empoyee reports, 1978. (Box 39)
  - Assistant Secretary for Financial Policy: Employment Commission, Virginia, 1978. (Box 39)
  - Assistant Secretary for Financial Policy: Employment reporting procedures, 1978. (Box 39)
  - Assistant Secretary for Financial Policy: Engineering and Buildings, Div. of, 1978. (Box 39)
  - Assistant Secretary for Financial Policy: Engineering and Buildings, Div. of - HB 1782, 1978. (Box 39)
  - Assistant Secretary for Financial Policy: Executive Orders and Policy Statements, 1978. (Box 39)
  - Assistant Secretary for Financial Policy: Expenditure Plan, Six Year, 1978. (Box 39)
  - Assistant Secretary for Financial Policy: Federal Executive Institute, 1978. (Box 39)
  - Assistant Secretary for Financial Policy: Federal infomration, 1978. (Box 39)
  - Assistant Secretary for Financial Policy: Fiscal Impact Statements, 1978. (Box 39)
  - Assistant Secretary for Financial Policy: Forecasts - Chase, 1978. (Box 39)
  - Assistant Secretary for Financial Policy: General Assembly - Member correspondence, 1978. (Box 39)
  - Assistant Secretary for Financial Policy: General Fund - Budget status, 1978. (Box 39)
  - Assistant Secretary for Financial Policy: General Fund - Projected revenues, 1978. (Box 39)
  - Assistant Secretary for Financial Policy: General Fund - Projected Special Fund revenues, 1978. (Box 39)
  - Assistant Secretary for Financial Policy: General Fund - Revenues, 1978. (Box 39)
  - Assistant Secretary for Financial Policy: General Services, Dept. of, 1978. (Box 39)
  - Assistant Secretary for Financial Policy: Governor's Office - Cabinet meeting minutes, 1976-1977. (Box 39)
  - Assistant Secretary for Financial Policy: Governor's Office - Cabinet meetings, 1978. (Box 39)
  - Assistant Secretary for Financial Policy: Governor's Office - Governor Dalton, 1978. (Box 39)
  - Assistant Secretary for Financial Policy: Governor's Office - People's Day / Cabinet meetings, 1978. (Box 39)
  - Assistant Secretary for Financial Policy: Governor's Office - Speeches and remarks, 1978. (Box 39)
  - Assistant Secretary for Financial Policy: Highway Fund Balance, 1978. (Box 40)
  - Assistant Secretary for Financial Policy: Highway Maintenance and Construction Fund, 1978. (Box 40)
  - Assistant Secretary for Financial Policy: Highways - General and Non-General Fund revenues, 1978. (Box 40)
  - Assistant Secretary for Financial Policy: House Appropriations - General, 1978. (Box 40)
  - Assistant Secretary for Financial Policy: House Appropriations - Monthly fiscal data, 1978. (Box 40)
  - Assistant Secretary for Financial Policy: HB 599, 1978. (Box 40)
  - Assistant Secretary for Financial Policy: House Committee assignments, 1978. (Box 40)
  - Assistant Secretary for Financial Policy: House Finance Committee, 1978. (Box 40)
  - Assistant Secretary for Financial Policy: Housing, Office of, 1978. (Box 40)
  - Assistant Secretary for Financial Policy: Human Resources, Secretary of, 1978. (Box 40)
  - Assistant Secretary for Financial Policy: Human Resources, Secretary of - HB 612 Study, 1978. (Box 40)
  - Assistant Secretary for Financial Policy: Human Resources, Secretary of - HJR 96, 1978. (Box 40)
  - Assistant Secretary for Financial Policy: ID Card Committee, 1978. (Box 40)
  - Assistant Secretary for Financial Policy: Industrial Development, Div. of, 1978. (Box 40)
  - Assistant Secretary for Financial Policy: Insurance Reserve Trust Fund, State, 1978. (Box 40)
  - Assistant Secretary for Financial Policy: Intergovernment Affairs, Dept. of, 1978. (Box 40)
  - Assistant Secretary for Financial Policy: Intergovernment Affairs, Dept. of - HB 1629, 1978. (Box 40)
  - Assistant Secretary for Financial Policy: Intergovernmental Relations, Advisory Committee on, 1978. (Box 40)
  - Assistant Secretary for Financial Policy: Joint Legislative Audit and Review Commission, 1978. (Box 40)
  - Assistant Secretary for Financial Policy: Kepone, 1978. (Box 40)
  - Assistant Secretary for Financial Policy: Legislation, 1978. (Box 40)
  - Assistant Secretary for Financial Policy: Legislation - Federal, 1978. (Box 40)
  - Assistant Secretary for Financial Policy: Legislative tracking, 1978. (Box 40)
  - Assistant Secretary for Financial Policy: Litter Control, 1978. (Box 41)
  - Assistant Secretary for Financial Policy: Loan authorizations, 1978. (Box 41)
  - Assistant Secretary for Financial Policy: Local Fiscal Impact Study Commission, 1978. (Box 41)
  - Assistant Secretary for Financial Policy: Local Government Advisory Council, 1978. (Box 41)
  - Assistant Secretary for Financial Policy: Local Government Officials Conference, 1978. (Box 41)
  - Assistant Secretary for Financial Policy: Management Analysis and Systems Development, Dept. of, 1978. (Box 41)
  - Assistant Secretary for Financial Policy: Manpower Utilization Plan (Administration and Finance), 1978. (Box 41)
  - Assistant Secretary for Financial Policy: Manpower Utilization Plan (Commerce and Resources), 1978. (Box 41)
  - Assistant Secretary for Financial Policy: Manpower Utilization Plan (Education), 1978. (Box 41)
  - Assistant Secretary for Financial Policy: Manpower Utilization Plan (Grants), 1978. (Box 41)
  - Assistant Secretary for Financial Policy: Manpower Utilization Plan (Human Resources), 1978. (Box 41)
  - Assistant Secretary for Financial Policy: Manpower Utilization Plan (Personnel), 1978. (Box 41)
  - Assistant Secretary for Financial Policy: Manpower Utilization Plan (Public Safety), 1978. (Box 41)
  - Assistant Secretary for Financial Policy: Manpower Utilization Plan (Transportation), 1978. (Box 41)
  - Assistant Secretary for Financial Policy: Manson, Jennifer Joy, 1978. (Box 41)
  - Assistant Secretary for Financial Policy: Marine Resources Commission, 1978. (Box 41)
  - Assistant Secretary for Financial Policy: Mental Health and Mental Retardation, Dept. of, 1978. (Box 41)
  - Assistant Secretary for Financial Policy: Miller, Ron (MIS Director) - SJR 104 Study, 1978. (Box 41)
  - Assistant Secretary for Financial Policy: Miscellaneous, 1978. (Box 41)
  - Assistant Secretary for Financial Policy: Municipal Finance Officers of America, 1978. (Box 41)
  - Assistant Secretary for Financial Policy: Municipal League, Virginia, 1978. (Box 41)
  - Assistant Secretary for Financial Policy: Murphy, Larry, 1978. (Box 41)
  - Assistant Secretary for Financial Policy: National Association of State Budget Officers (NASBO), 1978. (Box 41)
  - Assistant Secretary for Financial Policy: National Association of Tax Administrators (NATA), 1978. (Box 41)
  - Assistant Secretary for Financial Policy: National Governors Assocition, 1978. (Box 41)
  - Assistant Secretary for Financial Policy: National Tax Association (NTA), 1978. (Box 41)
  - Assistant Secretary for Financial Policy: Personnel and Training, Dept. of, 1978. (Box 41)
  - Assistant Secretary for Financial Policy: Personnel reports, 1978. (Box 41)
  - Assistant Secretary for Financial Policy: Planning and Budget, Dept. of, 1978. (Box 41)
  - Assistant Secretary for Financial Policy: Planning District Commissions, 1978. (Box 41)